{
  "decks": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "Rendering in React",
      "description": "React's component structure allows for quickly building a complex web application that relies on DOM manipulation. "
    },
    {
      "name": "React Router",
      "description": "React Router is a collection of navigational components that compose declaratively with your application.",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "asfgasgdasdgafhadfhadfhafha 67",
      "description": "afhgadfhafhasdfhafsdhafhafsdhafh 43",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "name": "zsdthhsgjh,jk.jdfhSFsdgh jh,jh,fgn",
      "description": "jhnfgmgj, hj.ujk./yujdl.dfyh.fyh.fhk.fhk.f.fhk.45e67547357357",
      "id": 4
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "front": "Differentiate between Real DOM and Virtual DOM. 4949",
      "back": "Virtual DOM updates are faster but do not directly update the HTML",
      "deckId": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "front": "How do you modify the state of a different React component?",
      "back": "Not at all! State is visible to the component only.",
      "deckId": 1
    },
    {
      "name": "asfgasgdasdgafhadfhadfhafha",
      "description": "afhgadfhafhasdfhafsdhafhafsdhafh 43",
      "id": 3,
      "cards": [
        {
          "front": "This is a card taht I am handleing",
          "back": "this is the back of the card",
          "deckId": 3,
          "id": 6
        },
        {
          "front": "blah blah blah",
          "back": "other blah blah",
          "deckId": 3,
          "id": 7
        },
        {
          "front": "zxcvzxcvzxcvbzsdfbzxdfbzxb",
          "back": "zdfbhzsdgjnsmkcfg,ghmxfghdfghzdfb",
          "deckId": 3,
          "id": 8
        }
      ],
      "front": "This is a card taht I am handleing 45"
    },
    {
      "front": "What path will match the follow Route?\n<Route>\n  <NotFound />\n</Route>",
      "back": "All paths. A route with no path matches all URL's",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "What does <Switch> do?",
      "back": "Renders the first matching child <Route> ",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "front": "This is a card taht I am handleing 45 57",
      "back": "this is the back of the card",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "front": "blah blah blah",
      "back": "other blah blah",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "front": "zxcvzxcvzxcvbzsdfbzxdfbzxb",
      "back": "zdfbhzsdgjnsmkcfg,ghmxfghdfghzdfb",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "front": "What is the render tag for React?",
      "back": "Render",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "front": "This is a new card",
      "back": "Hello this is a newish cardish",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "front": "This is a seccond new card ",
      "back": "this card is stupid",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "front": "Here is a new code",
      "back": "here is a new card",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 12
    }
  ]
}